var questions = {
  "Category 1": [
    {
      question: "Name Mickey’s pet dog",
      answer: "Pluto"
    }, {
        question: "Which dog is mickey’s friend that walks on two legs?",
        answer: "Goofy"
    }, {
        question: "What was the name of the puppy in the Fox and the Hound?",
        answer: "Copper"
    }, {
        question: "His name was Percy which movie was he from?",
        answer: "Pocahontas"
    }, {
        question: "Jock was what breed of Dog?",
        answer: "Scottish Terrier"
    }, {
        question: "Trusty a hound dog what was his job?",
        answer: "Tracking criminals through the swamps of Louisiana"
    }, {
        question: "Peridta’s mate is named?",
        answer: "Pongo"
    }, {
        question: "What dog believes he hs super popwers",
        answer: "BOLT"
    }, {
        question: "Name the cat who joined a bunch of New York Dogs",
        answer: "Oliver"
    }, {
        question: "Francis in Oliver and company is what kind of Dog?",
        answer: "Bulldog"
    }, {
        question: "Who is Todds best friend?",
        answer: "Copper"
    }, {
        question: "What kind of dog is Mel in the secret life of pets?",
        answer: "Pug"
    }, {
        question: "What was the name of the Jack Russsell terrier in the Secret Life of pets",
        answer: "Max"
    }, {
        question: "This animal was not a not a dog but went for a boat cruise in Moana",
        answer: "Rooster Chicken"
    }, {
        question: "What was the name of Prinec Eric’s dog in the Little Mermaid?",
        answer: "Max"
    }, {
        question: "What kind of Dog was Napolean from the Aristocats?",
        answer: "Bloodhound"
    }, {
        question: "What kind of dog was Lafayette?",
        answer: "A Basset Hound"
    }, {
        question: "what was the job of Napolean ?",
        answer: "Guard dogs on the farm"
    }, {
        question: "What was the name of the dog in Beauty and the Beast?",
        answer: "Sultan"
    }, {
        question: "What was the name of the dog in the Great mouse detective?",
        answer: "Toby"
    }, {
        question: "What was the name of the elderly Irish Wolfhound in the Fox and the Hound?",
        answer: "Chief"
    }, {
        question: "Which dog expresses himself thorugh a special high-tech translating collar?",
        answer: "Dug from UP"
    }, {
        question: "The name of The wealthy and slightly spoiled poodle of Oliver and Company?",
        answer: "Georgette"
    }, {
        question: "The name of the dog in who fell in love with a tramp?",
        answer: "Lady"
    }, {
        question: "Lucky is what from which movie?",
        answer: "A puppy from 101 Dalmations"
    }, {
        question: "Though not a real dog he is a dog thats long and wirey?",
        answer: "Slink from Toy Story"
    }, {
        question: "Though not a dog this character was introduced by his “mistress” as her dog?",
        answer: "Stich"
    }, {
        question: "What was the name of Cindereallas dog?",
        answer: "Bruno"
    }
  ],
  "Category 2": [
      {
          question: "What is the name of the country Prince Naveen (Disneys's The Frog and the Prince) from?",
          answer: "Maldonia"
      }, {
          question: "Who calls Jiminy Cricket a grasshopper in 'Pinocchio'?",
          answer: "Lampwick"
      }, {
          question: "What was the original title for the movie, 'Fantasia'?",
          answer: "Disney's Concert Magic "
      }, {
          question: "Whose shoulders does Dopey stand on in order to dance with Snow White during 'The Silly Song'?",
          answer: "Sneezy"
      }, {
          question: "What was Miss Bianca's partners name?",
          answer: "Bernard"
      }, {
          question: "What is the name of Merlin's pet owl in 'The Sword and the Stone'?",
          answer: "Archimedes"
      }, {
          question: "What was Mickey and Minnie Mouse original names?",
          answer: "Mortimer and Minerva "
      }, {
          question: "In 'The Little Mermaid', which name is NOT one of Ariel's sisters names?\nAndrina, Adora, Attina, and Alana?",
          answer: "Adora"
      }, {
          question: "What is Boo's real name?",
          answer: "Mary "
      }, {
          question: "What is the name of the mortal couple that adopts Hercules? Clio and Alcemmene, Amphitryon and Philodendra, Alcetis and Admetus, or Amphitryon and Alcemene?",
          answer: "Amphitryon and Alcemene"
      }, {
          question: "What is Jane's last name in Tarzan?",
          answer: "Porter"
      }, {
          question: "What is the name of the Reggae singing Caribbean crab in 'The Little Mermaid'?",
          answer: "Sebastian"
      }, {
          question: "Who teaches Mowgli the bare necessities of life?",
          answer: "Baloo"
      }, {
          question: "Which film does Eddie Murphy do the voice-over for a red Chinese dragon?",
          answer: "Mulan"
      }, {
          question: "Which 1991 Disney film has a female lead called Belle?",
          answer: "Beauty and the Beast"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney film is set on a Hawaiian Island?",
          answer: "Lilo and Stitch"
      }, {
          question: "Name the sidekick of Disney character, Pongo?",
          answer: "Perdita"
      }, {
          question: "What Disney film released in 2010 retells the classic fairytale Rapunzel?",
          answer: "Tangled"
      }, {
          question: "What is the name of Woody's owner in Toy Story?",
          answer: "Andy"
      }, {
          question: "The villain, Sid Phillips, appears in which 1995 Disney film?",
          answer: "Toy Story"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney character wants to be a 'real' boy?",
          answer: "Pinocchio"
      }, {
          question: "In which 1995 Disney film would you find Mr Potato Head voiced by Don Rickles?",
          answer: "Toy Story"
      }, {
          question: "Name the sidekick of Disney character, Timon?",
          answer: "Pumba"
      }, {
          question: "Name the well known Disney pair, Tarzan and ____?",
          answer: "Jane"
      }, {
          question: "Which Princess is in the Disney classic Aladdin?",
          answer: "Jasmine"
      }, {
          question: "What is the name of the orangutan I the Jungle Book?",
          answer: "King Louis"
      }, {
          question: "Name the well known Disney pair, Jiminy Cricket and ____?",
          answer: "Pinocchio"
      }, {
          question: "Name the sidekick of Disney character, Thumper?",
          answer: "Bambi"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney cub can not wait to be King?",
          answer: "Simba"
      }, {
          question: "What does Remy the rat in Ratatouille dream of becoming?",
          answer: "A French chef"
      }, {
          question: "What is the name of Donald Duck's Disney partner, who wore a red dress?",
          answer: "Daisy Duck"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney film is loosely based on the Knights of the Round Table?",
          answer: "Sword in the Stone"
      }, {
          question: "The character Princess Tiana is from which moive?",
          answer: "The Princess and the Frog"
      }, {
          question: "Name the well known Disney pair, Woody and ____?",
          answer: "Buzz Lightyear"
      }, {
          question: "Name this well known Disney pair, Chip and ?",
          answer: "Dale "
      }, {
          question: "In the film Finding Nemo, which city and country has Nemo been taken to?",
          answer: "(42 P. Sherman Wallaby Way) Sydney, Australia "
      }, {
          question: "What is the name of Mickey Mouse's Disney partner?",
          answer: "Minnie Mouse"
      }, {
          question: "What English City do Peter Pan and Wendy fly over?",
          answer: "London"
      }, {
          question: " In which Disney film does Angela Lansbury play a witch?",
          answer: "Bedknobs and Broom Sticks"
      }, {
          question: "Who keeps a watchful eye over Cinderella making her dreams come true?",
          answer: "The Fairy Godmother"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney film starts in the underwater world of Australia's Great Barrier Reef?",
          answer: "Finding Nemo"
      }, {
          question: "What is the name of Simba's Disney partner?",
          answer: "Nala"
      }, {
          question: "In which city is the 2007 Disney film Ratatouille based?",
          answer: "Paris"
      }, {
          question: "In Aladdin, what is the name of Jasmine's pet tiger?",
          answer: "Rajah"
      }, {
          question: "What is the name of the farm where the Barnstormer is located?",
          answer: "Goofy's Wise Acre Farm "
      }, {
          question: "What town is the setting for the Disney Movie 'The Love Bug?'",
          answer: "San Francisco"
      }, {
          question: "Before Mickey Mouse, what Disney character was suggested to be the Sorcerer's Apprentice in 'Fantasia'?",
          answer: "Dopey"
      }, {
          question: "What is the name of Donald Duck's sister",
          answer: "Dumbella"
      }, {
          question: "What was the first fairy tale that Walt Disney made a cartoon about?",
          answer: "Little Red Riding Hood"
      }, {
          question: "What was the name of the dragon in Mulan?",
          answer: "Mushu"
      }, {
          question: "In Lady & the Tramp, by what name did Tony call Tramp?",
          answer: "Butch"
      }, {
          question: "In the beginning of the animated feature Dumbo, they zoom in on a map of the US to the state where the circus goes for the winter, what state do they zoom in on?",
          answer: "Florida"
      }, {
          question: "What was the name of the whale in Pinocchio?",
          answer: "Monstro"
      }, {
          question: "In Alice in Wonderland, what is the name of Alice's kitten?",
          answer: "Dinah"
      }, {
          question: "What is the name of the nurse maid to the children in Peter Pan?",
          answer: "Nanna the Saint Bernard"
      }, {
          question: "What movie can the character named Diablo in and what is he?",
          answer: "Diablo can be found in Sleeping Beauty and is Maleficent's pet raven "
      }, {
          question: "Which is the only Disney animated film with a main character that doesn't speak?",
          answer: "Dumbo"
      }, {
          question: "What name did Princess Aurora use to hide her identity while living in the cottage in the woods?",
          answer: "Briar Rose"
      }, {
          question: "What are the names of the parents in Peter Pan?",
          answer: "George and Mary Darling "
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney princess makes a surprise appearance in the Hunchback of Notre Dame?",
          answer: "Belle"
      }, {
          question: "Which princess is known for wearing a green dress?",
          answer: "Tiana"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney princess wears pants rather than a dress?",
          answer: "Jasmine"
      }, {
          question: "Which princess attempts to disguise herself as a man?",
          answer: "Mulan"
      }, {
          question: "Which princess has a raccoon for a sidekick?",
          answer: "Pocahontas"
      }, {
          question: "Who was the first Disney princess based on a real historical figure?",
          answer: "Pocahontas"
      }, {
          question: "What country is Belle from in Beauty and the Beast?",
          answer: "France"
      }, {
          question: "Who was the first Disney princess?",
          answer: "Snow White"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney princess has no royal ties?",
          answer: "Mulan"
      }
  ],
  "Category 3": [
      {
          question: "Which organization do Bernard and Miss Bianca work for in “The Rescuers”?",
          answer: "The Rescue Aid Society"
      }, {
          question: "In “Lady and the Tramp,” why does Jim Dear give his wife Darling, Lady a gift?",
          answer: "Christmas Present"
      }, {
          question: "How long has Genie been trapped in the lamp?",
          answer: "10,000 years"
      }, {
          question: "When Alice encounters the White Rabbit, what is holding besides a pocket watch?",
          answer: "An Umbrella"
      }, {
          question: "How does Wendy first encounter Peter Pan?",
          answer: "She finds Peter Pan trying to attach his shadow with soap."
      }, {
          question: "Guess the number of pups Perdita gives birth to in the Disney classic “101 Dalmatians”?",
          answer: "15"
      }, {
          question: "Why is Flynn Rider wanted dead or alive?",
          answer: "He's a Thief"
      }, {
          question: "In “Sleeping Beauty,” what do the fairies give to Prince Phillip to fight Maleficent?",
          answer: "Sword of Truth and Shield of Virtue"
      }, {
          question: "How many bows are on the skirt of Cindirella’ pink dress",
          answer: "3"
      }, {
          question: "What is the time on the white rabbits pocket watch?",
          answer: "12:25"
      }, {
          question: "In 'The Rescuers', where is the Rescue Aid Society headquarters located?",
          answer: "The United Nations Building"
      }, {
          question: "In 'The Jungle Book', what did King Louis ask Mowgli to teach him?",
          answer: "How to be Human (And the secret behind making fire)"
      }, {
          question: "Captain Hook's has a hook on which hand?",
          answer: "Left"
      }, {
          question: "In 'Beauty and the Beast', how many eggs does Gaston eat for breakfast?",
          answer: "Five dozen "
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney Princess has the fewest number of lines?",
          answer: "Aura"
      }, {
          question: "What does Dumbo hold in his trunk to help him fly?",
          answer: "A magic feather"
      }, {
          question: "What animals portray surfer dudes in Finding Nemo?",
          answer: "Turtles"
      }, {
          question: "What are Scully and Mike collecting to power Monstropolis in Monsters, Inc.?",
          answer: "Childrens' Screams"
      }, {
          question: "Whose tea party does Alice attend?",
          answer: "The Mad Hatter's Party"
      }, {
          question: "What puts Snow White into a deep sleep?",
          answer: "A Poisoned Apple"
      }, {
          question: "What type of animal is a Flounder?",
          answer: "A Fish"
      }, {
          question: "What helps the medicine go down, in Mary Poppins?",
          answer: "A Spoonful of Sugar"
      }, {
          question: "What does Kaa in the Jungle Book do with his eyes?",
          answer: "Hypnotize"
      }, {
          question: "What does Ariel in The Little Mermaid give to Ursula so she can have legs?",
          answer: "Her voice"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney film is about a Mum and Daughter who swap places and are forced to live each others lives?",
          answer: "Freaky Friday"
      }, {
          question: "What animal swallowed a clock in Peter Pan?",
          answer: "A Crocodile"
      }, {
          question: "Name the rock on which Simba will stand as King in Lion King?",
          answer: "Pride Rock"
      }, {
          question: "In which short Disney film do we see Mickey Mouse lose control of Mops and Buckets?",
          answer: "The Sorcerers Apprentice"
      }, {
          question: "In which Disney film do you find a group of vegetarian sharks?",
          answer: "Finding Nemo"
      }, {
          question: "In Sleeping Beauty and Snow White the main characters are awoken by the same act - what is it?",
          answer: "A prince’s kiss"
      }, {
          question: "What Disney film has an Elastigirl and an Iceman?",
          answer: "The Incredibles"
      }, {
          question: "In the 1985 film Alice in Wonderland, what does the bottle with 'drink me' do to Alice?",
          answer: "Shrinks her"
      }, {
          question: "What is Aladdin's main type of magical transport?",
          answer: "Majic Carpet"
      }, {
          question: "Which 1973 animated Disney film has its main character played by a fox?",
          answer: "Robin Hood"
      }, {
          question: "What did Jasmin steal from the marketplace?",
          answer: "An Apple"
      }, {
          question: "What does Aladdin, and a reluctant Abu, give the beggar children to eat?",
          answer: "Bread"
      }, {
          question: "When does Mary Poppins say she will leave the Banks’ house?",
          answer: "When the Wind Changes"
      }, {
          question: "What is the motto for the Rescue Aid Society in The Rescuers?",
          answer: "We Never Fail to do What is Right"
      }, {
          question: "In Dumbo, where is Mrs. Jumbo when the stork delivers her baby?",
          answer: "In the Circus Train"
      }, {
          question: "After being on earth, where did Hercules first meet his father Zeus?",
          answer: "In the Temple of Zeus "
      }, {
          question: "In Toy Story, what game does the slinky play?",
          answer: "Checkers"
      }, {
          question: "In Mary Poppins, what animal was on the end of Mary Poppins’ umbrella that spoke?",
          answer: "A Parrot"
      }, {
          question: "In Hercules, Hades promised not to harm Megara provided that Hercules give up his strength. How long did he have to agree to give up his strength for?",
          answer: "24 Hours"
      }, {
          question: "What Disney Full Length Animated Feature was released in only 14 theaters throughout the world",
          answer: "Fantasia"
      }, {
          question: "During the ballroom scene of Beauty & the Beast, what color is Belle’s Gown?",
          answer: "Gold"
      }, {
          question: "What was the first Disney Full Length Animated Feature that used the wide screen process of Cinema Scope?",
          answer: "Lady & the Tramp"
      }, {
          question: "In Bambi, what word does the owl use to describe falling in love?",
          answer: "Twitterpatted"
      }, {
          question: "In the Little Mermaid when Ariel sees Prince Eric, what type of celebration was happening on the ship?",
          answer: "A Birthday Party"
      }, {
          question: "In the Aristocats, what kind of truck does O’Malley spot to give Dutchess and the kittens a ride back to Paris in?",
          answer: "A Milk Truck"
      }, {
          question: "What is the crew celebrating on the ship at the beginning of The Little Mermaid?",
          answer: "Prince Eric’s Birthday"
      }, {
          question: "How long has the curse been over the castle in Beauty and the Beast?",
          answer: "10 years"
      }, {
          question: "What time does the royal ball start in Cinderella?",
          answer: "8 p.m."
      }, {
          question: "What animal does the sultan’s throne resemble in Aladdin?",
          answer: "An Elephant"
      }, {
          question: "What color hair does Eric think his rescuer has in The Little Mermaid?",
          answer: "Black or a Dark Color"
      }, {
          question: "According to Disney what is Cinderella’s name?",
          answer: "Ella (Mary Beth Ella Gertrude)"
      }, {
          question: "Who was Lumiere’s girlfriend?",
          answer: "Featherduster"
      }, {
          question: "Name one of the two of Cinderella’s Stepsisters…",
          answer: "Anastasia and Drizella"
      }, {
          question: "The character from which movie says have courage and be kind before she dies?",
          answer: "Said by Cinderella’s mother"
      }, {
          question: "What is Ariel’s daughter’s name?",
          answer: "Melody"
      }, {
          question: "What was the mother cats name in the Aristocats?",
          answer: "Dutches"
      }, {
          question: "What was the name of the black kitten in the Aristocats?",
          answer: "Beriloz"
      }
  ], 
  "Category 4": [
      {
          question: "Finish the lyrics to this song from 'The Little Mermaid': 'Wouldn’t you think I’m the girl, the girl who has everything? Look at this trove, treasures untold...'",
          answer: "'How many wonders can one cavern hold?'"
      }, {
          question: "Finish these 'Frozen' lyrics: 'My soul is spiraling in frozen fractals all around…'",
          answer: "'And one thought crystallizes like an icy blast.'"
      }, {
          question: "Which of the seven dwarves DIDN’T sing 'Heigh Ho'?",
          answer: "Dopey"
      }, {
          question: "What was Wall-E's favourite musical?",
          answer: "Hello Dolly"
      }, {
          question: "The song 'Where Do I Go From Here?' is in which animated sequel?",
          answer: "Pochahontas II"
      }, {
          question: "In which Disney film will you hear the song 'Everybody Wants To Be A Cat'?",
          answer: " The Aristocats"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney character sings the song 'Be Prepared'?",
          answer: "Scar"
      }, {
          question: "'Two Worlds' is a song from which Disney film?",
          answer: "Tarzan"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney character sings the song 'Poor Unfortunate Souls'?",
          answer: "Ursula"
      }, {
          question: "Name the Disney character that sang, 'One Day My Prince Will Come'?",
          answer: "Snow White"
      }, {
          question: "Which character, in the film Dumbo, sings the song 'Baby Mine'?",
          answer: "Dumbos Mum"
      }, {
          question: "In Sebatian’s song what does he want Prince Eric to do to Ariel in The Little Mermaid?",
          answer: "Kiss her"
      }, {
          question: "Which duet sung by Princess Jasmine and Aladdin appears in the film, Aladdin?",
          answer: "A Whole New World"
      }, {
          question: "'Can You Feel The Love Tonight' is a song from which Disney film?",
          answer: "Lion King"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney character sings the song 'Trust In Me'?",
          answer: "Kaa from the Jungle Book"
      }, {
          question: "Who, in the film Sword in the Stone, sings the song 'Higitus Figitus'?",
          answer: "Merlin"
      }, {
          question: "In which Disney film will you hear the song 'Reflection'?",
          answer: "Mulan"
      }, {
          question: "In which Disney film will you hear the song 'You Can Fly'?",
          answer: "Peter Pan"
      }, {
          question: "Which film will you hear 'Colours of the Wind' sung?",
          answer: "Pocahontas"
      }, {
          question: "'Once Upon a Dream' is a song from which Disney film?",
          answer: "Sleeping Beauty"
      }, {
          question: "What song contains the lyrics 'Up where they walk, up where they run, up where they spend all day in the sun'?",
          answer: "'Part of your World', The Little Mermaid"
      }, {
          question: "What is the name of Disney's 1940 musical masterpiece which combines classical music and animation?",
          answer: "Fantasia"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney character sings the song 'Mother Knows Best'?",
          answer: "Mother Gothel, Tangled"
      }, {
          question: "What Disney film contains the classic song 'Be our Guest'?",
          answer: "Beauty and the Beast"
      }, {
          question: "'One Jump' is a song from which Disney film?",
          answer: "Aladdin"
      }, {
          question: "In which Disney film will you hear the song 'He's a Tramp'?",
          answer: "Lady & the Tramp"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney character sings the song 'Who's Been Painting My Rose Red'?",
          answer: "Queen of Hearts, Alice in Wonderland"
      }
  ],
  "Category 5": [
      {
          question: "In which animated feature would you find a villain named Sykes?",
          answer: "Oliver and Cmpany"
      }, {
          question: "In which Disney film will you find the villain, Cruella De Vil?",
          answer: " 101 Dalmations"
      }, {
          question: "The villain, The Queen of Hearts, appears in which 1951 Disney film?",
          answer: "Alice in Wonderland"
      }, {
          question: "Which Disney classic has a talking mirror which is asked 'mirror mirror on the wall'?",
          answer: "Snow White"
      }, {
          question: "The villain, Madame Mim, appears in which 1963 Disney film?",
          answer: "The Sword and the Stone"
      }, {
          question: "In which Disney film will you hear the song 'Zero To Hero'?",
          answer: "Hercules"
      }, {
          question: "In which 1998 Disney film will you find the villain, Shan-Yu?",
          answer: "Mulan"
      }, {
          question: "Name the villain that was named after a real car?",
          answer: "Cruela DeVille (De Ville)"
      }, {
          question: "The villain, Gaston, appears in which 1991 Disney film?",
          answer: "Beauty and the Beast"
      }, {
          question: "In which 1992 Disney rendition film will you find the villain, Jafar?",
          answer: "Aladdin"
      }, {
          question: "In which Disney film will you find the villain, Scar?",
          answer: "Lion King"
      }, {
          question: "he villain, Hopper, appears in which Disney film?",
          answer: "A Bug’s Life"
      }, {
          question: "The villain, Prince John, appears in which 1973 Disney film?",
          answer: "Robin Hood"
      }, {
          question: "In which Disney film will you find the villain, Ursula?",
          answer: "The Little Mermaid"
      }, {
          question: "The villain, Randall Boggs, appears in which Disney film?",
          answer: " Monsters, Inc."
      }, {
          question: "What type of animal is Kaa from The Jungle Book?",
          answer: "A Python / Snake"
      }
  ],
  "Category 6": [{
    mp3: 1,
    question: " question1 ",
    answer: " answer1 "
  }, {
    mp3: 2,
    question: " question2 ",
    answer: " answer2 "
  }, {
    mp3: 3,
    question: " question3 ",
    answer: " answer3 "
  }, {
    mp3: 4,
    question: " question4 ",
    answer: " answer4 "
  }, {
    mp3: 5,
    question: " question5 ",
    answer: " answer5 "
  }, {
    mp3: 6,
    question: " question6 ",
    answer: " answer6"
  }]
};
